Matt: it's finding a lot of verbal
expression ambiguous because very
often there is contextual information.
Whether that be body language, facial
expressions, or if it's something
else, someone knows that for instance
we're in work and we're dealing with
a particular piece of work even though
we've got lots of other things going on.
And so they expect me to be kind of
automatically know what they're talking
about and while sort of neuro- typical
colleagues might easily understand that
I may well have to ask and ask again.
This does go both ways though, I do
find I'll say something which I think
is perfectly clear because I've been
very precise, but because the person
I'm speaking to is expecting there to be
something that they're going to need to
decode or figure out they might completely
misunderstand what it is I've said